This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era, and countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece, the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum-gum fruit, set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles, they capture the unwanted attention of the world government, which will use any means necessary to stop them.
This sight!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue, the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
After being separated from his crew, Luffy set out to rescue his captured brother, Ace.
To do so, he snuck into the government prison, Impel Down.
Along the way, he ran into Buggy the Clown, as well as Mr. Three, a former Baroque Works agent.
Together, they descended into the depths of the prison.
This is level three, the starvation hell.
In other words, let's move while we have the sweat to spare!
Okay, we must go to level four already!
Give me a Sphinx!
The Sphinx is awake!
Impart Noodle!
Gah, gah, gah, gah, gah, gah, gah!
Meanwhile, Boa Hancock, who helped Luffy break into Impel Down, drew ever closer to the floor where Ace is being held prisoner.
The Sphinx is a prisoner!
A, de, hurrah!
Hm?
Hey! Who's that singing?
A, de, hurrah!
Huh?
The Unleashed Swan, a reunion with Bon Clay.
Oh, come my way.
Oh, oh, oh, come my way.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, come my way.
I can barely stand in this heat, but that guy's singing like he's at somebody's birthday party.
If he's a prisoner here, he must be tough as hell.
I know this voice.
I know this song.
Hey, partner.
I think this guy can help us out.
Wait, what?
Let's discuss this first.
Oh, come my way.
Spin, spin, oh, come my way.
Keep it up, boys.
Spin and spin like you're caught up in the time of the times.
Hurry, this way.
Wait, listen.
I don't think we should.
Come on, lazy bones.
The party's just getting started.
If you think it's steamy in here now, you'll really hate it when I'm angry.
Oh, Mr. Three, how are you?
Well, this is awkward.
What the?
Mr. Three!
Wait just a minute here.
What are you doing in Impel Down?
You're behind bars, so you must have been caught, right?
No, no.
I'm the one who's behind bars, aren't I?
How did you like my one-of-a-kind double take?
It's a Kenpo special technique called looking back on that autumn night's dream.
Hey, what the hell is this strange creature?
Hard to say.
Let's be sure to not let it out.
Oh, don't be mean.
I've got way too much energy to stay cooped up in here.
How's it going to get?
Whatever.
As long as I keep going down, I'm sure I'll find where they've got a sooner or later.
Ah!
He headed downstairs?
You're sure of that?
You saw him go?
You're not pulling my tail, are you?
Heh, no.
Of course not.
Very well, and thank you ever so much for letting me out of that cell, Mr. Three.
I'll pay you back sometime.
Huh?
Now then.
I'm on my way, my friend.
Oh, come my way.
All the way to hell and back.
That worked out well for everyone.
Uh-huh.
Our security here is legendary.
How was he able to slip through?
And though he's just one invader, if we let him rescue Ace, not only will it be the ultimate humiliation for him held down, but for the entire world government.
We can't let that happen.
In the name of Navy headquarters.
We're going to head into that prison and stop Straw Hat Luffy no matter what it takes.
Sir!
Hold on a moment.
Huh?
Who goes there?
I'm Mistress Sadie, our torture expert.
We've already been compromised, so accepting the help of the Navy would just further disgrace.
Hmm.
The good name of Impel Down.
Mistress? Really?
What, does she think she's being cute or something?
I'm adorable!
You will refer to me as Mistress!
Those screams are irresistible.
Why, you?
Hold it. Are you telling me you don't need the Navy's aid?
Yes. This whole prison is a labyrinthine hell.
If you don't know your way around in here, you'll be of no help to us.
That being said, if you wish to serve us, you can guard the outside.
This drawbridge is the only entrance.
We'll secure ourselves inside, raise it, and...
...seal off Impel Down completely.
We'll do our job. And as long as you do yours, nobody...
Ah. We'll escape from this prison alive.
Fair enough. We'll remain here and guard the gate then.
There. That's a good boy.
Is that a...
No way.
Koala?
A koala?
Sure is.
Not gonna be a슬.
Let's see.
Impel Down is now completely sealed off.
Huh?
A koala?
Hannibal?
Yeah, and Magellan's here too. What's going on?
You've got a special visitor, Ace. Behave yourself.
You'll never guess who it is. Jimbei.
You know her well, but even you've never met her.
Maybe I should give Ace here a hint.
Her name is notorious, but she never shows herself.
She leads a tribe of warriors called the Kuja.
And she's one of the seven warlords of the sea.
Strong, noble, and the most beautiful woman in the world.
The pirate empress, Boa Hancock.
Yay! It's Hancock! Check her out!
Hey, quick question. When I become warden,
will you do me the honor of being my beautiful bride?
Marry me!
Ooh! Ouch!
When I'm warden, I'll hit on her all I want.
I mean, sorry, warden, you can hit me all you want.
That's enough of your tomfoolery.
Woo! Holy crap!
Guys, the Mycene thing, she's gorgeous!
So she's the snake princess of Kuja.
Hey! Move a little closer!
Turn around, Hancock!
Yeah! That is some choice meat!
Hey, hot stuff! Come to our cell.
We'll give you some 10-11 like you've never had before.
Damn! She smells amazing!
If I ever get out of here, I'm going straight to Amazon Lily!
I heard it's full of hot, naked chicks.
Count me in!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha!
What is it? What do you want from me?
Nothing, really.
I simply wanted to take a good look at you.
To see the cause of the war I will take part in firsthand.
That's all.
Am I everything you'd hoped for?
Come on, Hancock! Don't ignore us like that!
Get over here and give me some!
Ha ha ha ha!
In the past, you've always been the empress
who stood her ground and disobeyed every summons.
Yet you're going to take part in this war?
Ha ha ha!
I hope your title is worth your dignity.
A pleasure to meet you, too.
Now mind your foolish tongue.
Oh man, I want to lick her everywhere!
They're trying to talk.
Keep it down, damp lout.
Can it, Magellan?
Or should I say diarrhea man?
Ha ha ha ha!
Nice one!
Say, Snake Princess,
I bet the women on your island are hungry for guys like us!
Hey, you!
Why don't you make Hannibal the Warden?
Really, now?
Come on, Hancock!
Move that sexy ass over to our cell already!
I'll only say this once.
Hancock, look at me!
If you keep accosting me with those coarse voices,
I'll get scared.
I can't take it!
She's so cute!
She's perfect!
Let us have her, diarrhea man!
If there's a more vile place in this world,
I don't want to see it.
This makes me sick.
Everyone's calling you diarrhea man,
and you just put up with it.
It's disgraceful.
If that's your attitude,
I know a guy who'd love to have your job.
Oh, so cute!
Diarrhea man, for shame!
Enough.
She's hot!
Let me have her for myself, diarrhea man!
Diarrhea man!
Let me show her my snake!
I won't tolerate your impertinence any longer.
This ends now.
Oh, one Magellan!
Wait a second, please!
You're going to kill us, too!
Ah!
You are going to suffer.
No!
We're dead!
Your degenerate seem to have forgotten your place.
Let me remind you who the boss is around here.
Man, he is pissed!
He's brought out the Hydra!
Wait, what are you doing?
Mark Magellan, stop!
Please!
Come on!
We were just joking around!
Honest!
Ah!
No!
You bastard!
You can't do this to me!
Wow, sorry, buddy.
You're a dead man now.
Ah!
Dammit!
I need the antidote!
Help me!
Ah!
Never forget that I have not only the authority, but also the ability to execute any one of you at my whim.
There. So sorry about that. You're free to speak with him now. Proceed.
I'm finished here.
Wait! Is what you just told me the truth?
What reason would I have to lie?
By the way, he was afraid you might be angry, but he still had to do it.
Is that really all you needed?
What do you think they were talking about?
I have no idea. Honestly, I was busy trying to get away from you.
So, Ace, will you tell me what she said to you?
She said that my brother is here.
Huh? You mean Luffy? The one with the straw hat that you're always talking about? That fool!
Oh, man! When the heck did I start going upstairs? I want to go downstairs!
Well, if it started going up, it'll probably go back down again sooner or later.
I'm getting hungry.
I've got an image of him, and it appears he's about to enter District C.
Right. We'll see him.
They're using Sea Prism Stone Nuts again.
Close one!
Oh, crap! It's that lion thing!
Hey! Let him go!
Need a hand, pal?
Hey! Zoro!
Ha-ha! Fooled ya!
That is not Zoro, but he does sound familiar.
Been a while, Straw Boy?
Did you miss me, old pal?
And try to open the plume.
Well, did everyone enjoy my very special secret talent?
Oh, yeah!
It's meant to be true!
Running now would go against everything
Port Clay stands for.
If we abandon allies who are risking their lives
to pick up a friend,
could we live ourselves tomorrow?
Oh, Miss Hina, the enemy ships are splitting up.
You must be feeling pretty stupid right now
valling for such a simple trick.
See, we're masters of disguise.
As well as friends to the Straw Hats.
Bring it on, sister.
I promise you, Port Clay,
we will never forget you.
It's Bon!
I'd still rather have Zorro,
but I'm glad you're alive after all that happened!
Tiki, open fire on Straw Hat!
Piss off!
Bastards!
You stay away from my friend,
or things are about to get fed up!
Good boy, Sphinx.
Now, take them out.
There!
After a beating like that,
he shouldn't be bothering us anymore.
Sometimes, when you're dealing with an animal,
you have to teach it the law of the jungle.
Fried noodles.
You really bailed us out last time,
but I thought for sure you were dead!
Am I ever happy to see you!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Oh, stop pulling my tail!
You know swans never die!
Unless that isn't true!
Ha ha ha ha!
And now a reminder of how Bon Clay's power works.
He ate the clone clone fruit,
allowing him to transform into anyone
whose face is touched with his right hand.
He was able to turn into Zorro
because he had touched him before,
but he is not able to mimic his strength.
Now there's another escapee to deal with.
The deeper the straw hat descends,
the more frenzy seems to pick up along the way.
Lugari, I don't care what it takes.
Don't let them escape.
Oh, and by the way,
I heard that you wanted to go all the way down to level five.
That's the plan, but I can use a guide if you're not too busy.
Wouldn't have it any other way, my friend.
As fate would have it, there's someone down on level five
I'd like to see, too.
Really?
Now then, shall we go?
Let's do it!
Teaming up with Bon Clay,
Luffy races from level three to level four,
pummeling every blue goodie that dares to stand in their path.
But all good things must come to an end,
and the powerful demon guard Minotaurus
is ready to do some pummeling of his own.
On the next One Piece,
Warden Magellan's strategy,
straw hat entrapment completed,
I'm going to be king of the pirates!